Alfred J. Frueh
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Art Work, circa 1906-1961, undated, Series 4:; (Boxes 2-3, 6, OV 8-9; 1.5 linear ft.)
  - By Frueh, 1920-1962, undated, Subseries 4.1:
    - Fabray - Foy, 1947, undated (Box 2)
      Fontanne, Lynn (see also: Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne)
      Forbes, Meriel
      Ford, Paul and Wynn Miller
      Ford, Ruth
      Forsythe, John
      Fox, Harry
      Foy, Eddie
    - Caricatures, Fraerman - Gazzara, 1959, undated (Box 2)
      Fraerman, T.
      Frelinghuysen, Senator of New Jersey
      Frey, Nathaniel
      Frueh, Alfred
      Frueh, Giuliette
      Gallagher, Helen
      Gautier, Dick
      Gaxton, William
      Gazzara, Ben
    - Caricatures, George - Guinness, circa 1926-1962, undated (Box 2)
      George, Grace
      Geringer, Robert
      Ghostly, Alice
      Gibson, Virginia
      Gilbert, Lou
      Gilmore, Margola
      Gingold, Hermoine
      Gleason, Jackie
      Goodwin, Nat C.
      Gordon, Peyton (Teapot Dome/Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial)
      Gordon, Ruth
      Gorse, John
      Graham, William
      Green, Adolph
      Greenstein, Milton
      Griffies, Ethel
      Griffith, Andy
      Griffith, Hugh
      Grimes, Tammy
      Guetary, Georges
      Guinness, Alec
    - Caricatures, Hagen - Hewitt, 1956, undated (Box 2)
      Hagen, Uta
      Haigh, Kenneth
      Haladay
      Haley, Jack
      Hall, George
      Hall, Juanita
      Hamilton, Nancy
      Hammerstein, Oscar
      Hammond, Ruth
      Hampden, Walter
      Harrigan, William
      Harris, Julie
      Harrison, Rex
      Hartman, Paul (see also: Box 6)
      Hayes, Helen (see also: Portman, Eric and Helen Hayes)
      Heckart, Eileen
      Heflin, Van
      Heining, Violet
      Helmore, Tom
      Henderson, Florence
      Hepburn, Audrey
      Hepburn, Katherine
      Hert, Alvin T., of Kentucky
      Hewer, John
      Hewitt, Alan
    - Caricatures, Hicks - Howard, 1949-1957, undated (Box 2)
      Hicks, Russell
      Hill, Arthur (see also: "A Death in the Family")
      Hiller, Wendy
      Hindemuth, Paul
      Hingle, Pat
      Hitchcock, Frank
      Hitchcock, Raymond
      Hitchcock, Senator
      Hitler, Adolf
      Hodiak, John
      Hoffman, Jane
      Holden, Peter (see: Digges, Dudley and Peter Holden)
      Holliday, Judy
      Holm, Celeste
      Homolka, Oscar (see also: Box 6)
      Hooker, Elon H.
      Hope, Bob
      Horne, Lena
      "The Hostage" (Avis Bunnage, Alfred Lynch, Celia Salkeld, and Maxwell Shaw)
      Howard, Eugene ("Willie")
      Howard, John
      Howard, Leslie
    - Caricatures, Huber - Kaye, 1920, undated (Box 2)
      Huber, Gusti
      Hughes, Governor
      Hull, Cordell
      Hull, Josephine
      Hunt, Martita
      Hunter, Kim (see also: Tandy, Jessica with Marlon Brando, Karl Malden, and Kim Hunter)
      Hurst, Fanny
      Hyman, Earle
      Ingram, Ralph
      Itow, Michio
      Ives, Burl
      Jaffe
      Jessel, Patricia
      Johan, Zita
      Johnson, Hiram
      Johnson, Richard
      Johnson, William
      Joslyn, Allyn
      Karlan, Michael
      Karloff, Boris
      Kaye, Danny
    - Caricatures, Keith - Lawrence, 1957, undated (Box 3)
      Keith, Robert
      Kelley, Gene
      Kelly, Nancy
      Kelly, Paul
      Kennedy, Arthur (see also: Dunnock, Mildred with Mitchell Cameron and Arthur Kennedy; and Box 6)
      Kerr, Deborah
      Kerr, John
      Keyserling, Harold
      Kimbrough, Clinton
      Klugman, Jack
      Lahr, Bert
      Lamas, Fernando
      Landis, Judge
      Lane, Beaufory
      Lane, Gloria
      Lane, Katherine
      Lansbury, Angela
      Larrimore, Francine
      Laurence, Paula
      Lawrence, Eddie
      Lawrence, Gertrude (see also: Box 6)
    - Caricatures, Lee - Lyons, circa 1926-1956, undated (Box 3)
      Lee, Canada
      Le Gallienne, Eva
      Lehman, Madam
      Lenard, Mark
      Lenya, Lotte
      Leontovich, Eugenie
      Leroy, Hal
      Lester, Jerry
      Lillie, Beatrice
      Lilo
      Lindsay, Howard (see also: Box 6)
      Littleton, Martin (Teapot Dome/Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial)
      Lobrono, Gus
      Locke, Katherine
      Logan, Ella (see: Box 6)
      Long, F.
      Lopokova, Lydia
      Lord, Pauline
      Losee, Charles
      Love, Phyllis
      Lovejoy, Frank
      Lucas, Paul
      Lucas, Paul and Lucille Watson
      Lunt, Alfred
      Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne
      Lynch, Alfred (see also: "The Hostage")
      Lynn, Judy
      Lynn, William
      Lyons, George
    - Caricatures, MacDonnell-Mayehoff, 1922-1961, undated (Box 3)
      MacDonnell, Kyle
      MacGrath, Luveen
      MacMahon, Aline
      Makeham, Elliot
      Malden, Karl (see also: Tandy, Jessica, with Marlon Brando and Kim Hunter)
      Mansfield, Richard
      Manuelian, Ethel
      March, Frederic
      Margetson, Arthur
      Marino, Joseph
      Marley, Enid
      Marlowe, Gloria
      Marshall, E. G.
      Marshall, Sarah
      Martin, Mary
      Martin, Senator of New Jersey
      Massaquer, Conrad
      Massey, Raymond (see also: Box 6)
      Matteson, Ruth
      Matthews, Carmen
      Matthews, George
      May, Elaine and Mike Nichols
      Mayehoff, Eddie
    - Caricatures, McArthur - McVey, undated (Box 3)
      McArthur, Jane
      McCarthy, Mary
      McCauley, Jack
      McCormick, Myron
      McCormick, Senator
      McCracken, Joan
      McDowall, Roddy
      McGavin, Darren
      McGiver, John
      McGrath, Paul
      McKay, Scott
      McKenna, Siobhan
      McLerie, Allyn
      McMahon, Aline (see: "A Death in the Family")
      McMahon, Horace (see also: Mundy, Meg and Horace McMahon)
      McNeil, Claudia
      McVey, Patrick
    - Caricatures, Meacham - Musgrove, 1962, undated (Box 3)
      Meacham, Anne (see also: Box 6)
      Medford, Kay
      Meeker, Ralph
      Meiser, Edith
      Mengelberg, Willem
      Menken, Helen
      Meredith, Burgess
      Merivale, Phillip (see also: Box 6)
      Merkel, Una
      Merman, Ethel
      Miller, Wynn (see: Ford, Paul and Wynn Miller)
      Mitchell, Grant
      Mitchell, Thomas (see: Box 6)
      Mohyeddin, Zia
      Montalaban, Ricardo
      Monterey, Carlotta
      Moore, Victor
      Morley, Robert
      Morse, Robert
      Mostel, Zero
      Mulvane, David, National Committeeman from Kansas
      Mundy, Meg and Horace McMahon
      Muni, Paul
      Munsey
      Musgrove, Gertrude
      National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc. (see: American Brotherhood)
    - Caricatures, Natwick - Oskar, 1907-1957, undated (Box 3)
      Natwick, Mildred
      Nazimova, Alla
      Neal, Patricia
      Neff, Hildegarde
      Nesbitt, Kathleen
      New, Senator of Indiana
      Neway, Patricia
      Nichols, Mike (see also: May, Elaine and Mike Nichols)
      Niesen, Gertrude
      Niki
      Nixon, Richard
      Nolan, Lloyd
      Nugent, Elliott
      Nuyen, France
      Nype, Russell
      Olaff, Pierre (see: Brossett, Colette and Pierre Olaff)
      O'Malley, Rex
      O'Neal, Patrick
      O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (see: Monterey)
      O'Neill, James
      Orbach, Jerry
      Orlaf, Pierre
      Oskar
    - Caricatures, Pach - Povah, 1957, undated (Box 3)
      Pach, Walter
      Page, Geraldine
      Palance, Walter Jack (see: Box 6)
      Palmer, Lili
      Parsons, Herbert
      Pastene, Robert
      Peel, Eileen
      Perkins, Anthony
      Perkins, Osgood (see also: Clarke, Ina and Osgood Perkins)
      Pidgeon, Walter
      Pinza, Ezio
      Platt, Louise
      Pleasence, Donald
      Poindexter, Senator
      Poitier, Sidney
      Polan, Lou
      Polk, Gordon
      Pollack, Channing
      Portman, Eric (see also: Box 6)
      Portman, Eric and Helen Hayes
      Povah, Phyllis
      Premice, Josephine (see: Dancing Figures)
    - Caricatures, Preston - Ritchard, 1957-1962, undated (Box 3)
      Preston, Robert
      Price, Vincent
      Prince, William
      Prokofiev, Sergei (see: Box 6)
      Rahn, Muriel
      Rains, Claude
      Randell, Ron
      Rathbone, Basil
      Rawlings, Margarey
      Raymond, Helen
      Redgrave, Michael
      Reed, Florence (see: Taylor, Laurette and Florence Reed, Box 6)
      Reid, Carl Benton
      Reilly, Charles Nelson
      Rennie, James
      Revere, Anne
      Rich, Irene
      Richardson, Ralph
      Richman, Mark
      Ritchard, Cyril
    - Caricatures, Robards - Russell, circa 1926-1956, undated (Box 3)
      Robards, Jason
      Roberts, Owen (Teapot Dome/Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial)
      Robeson, Paul
      Robinson, Bartlett
      Robinson, Bill "Bojangles"
      Robinson, Judith
      Robinson, Senator
      Rodgers, Douglas F.
      Rodgers, Will
      Roosevelt, Eleanor
      Rose, George
      Ross
      Ross, Anthony
      Rule, Janice (see also: Box 6)
      Russell, Rosalind
    - Caricatures, Salkeld - Sherwood, circa 1926-1961, undated (Box 3)
      Salkeld, Celia (see also: "The Hostage")
      Salmi, Albert
      Santelli
      Savo, Jimmy
      Schildkraut, Joseph
      Schnabel, Stefan
      Scofield, Paul (see: Decker, Albert and Paul Scofield)
      Scott, George C.
      Scott, Martha
      Scourby, Alexander
      Segal, Vivienne (see also: Box 6)
      Seldes, Marian
      Shatner, William
      Shaw, Maxwell (see also: "The Hostage")
      Shaw, Robert
      Shean, Al
      Sherman, Hiram
      Sherwood, Robert Emmet
      "Show Boat" (see: Box 6)
    - Caricatures, Siddons - Strudwich, 1920-1957, undated (Box 3)
      Siddons, Frederick L. (Teapot Dome/Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial)
      Silvers, Phil
      Simms, Hilda
      Skinner, Otis
      Slezak, Walter
      Smith, Alfred E.
      Smith, Kent
      Smith, Muriel (see: Box 6)
      Smoot, Senator
      Sokoloff, Vladimir
      Spearman, Rawn
      Sproul, Governor of Pennsylvania
      Stander, Lionell
      Stanley, Kim
      Stapleton, Maureen
      Steiger, Rod
      Stevens, Mark
      Stewart, Donald Ogden
      Stewart, John
      Stickney, Dorothy (see also: Box 6)
      Stone, Fred
      Stone, Dorothy
      Straight, Beatrice
      Strasberg, Susan
      Strauss, Robert
      Stritch, Elaine
      Strudwich, Shepperd
    - Caricatures, Sullivan - Taylor, circa 1926-1927, undated (Box 3)
      Sullivan, Francis L.
      Sullivan, Margaret
      Sullivan, Pat, Committeeman from Wyoming
      Swann, Donald
      Swanson, Gloria
      Sydney, Basil
      Tabbert, William
      Taft, Charles P.
      Talva, Galina
      Tamiroff, Akim
      Tandy, Jessica
      Tandy, Jessica with Marlon Brando, Karl Malden, and Kim Hunter
      Taylor, Laurette (see also: Dowling, Eddie and Laurette Taylor; and Box 6)
      Taylor, Laurette and Flornce Reed (see: Box 6)
    - Caricatures, Tearle - Voskovec, circa 1926-1927, undated (Box 3)
      Teapot Dome/Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial (see: Denby, Edwin, Former Secretary of the Navy; Dohoney, Robert; Gordon, Peyton; Littleton, Martin; Roberts, Owen; Siddons, Frederick L.; Thomas, Charles S.)
      Tearle, Gorden
      Thomas, Charles S. (Teapot Dome/Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial)
      [Thomas, Gomez?]
      Thompson, Denman
      Thompson, William Hale
      Tone, Franchot
      Tracy, Lee
      Traubel, Helen
      Treacher, Arthur
      Tucker, Sophie
      Tumultz, Joe
      Tyler, Judy
      Upshaw, Congressman of Georgia
      Ure, Mary (see: Box 6)
      Vallee, Rudy
      Van Dyke, Dick
      Van Dyke, Marcia
      Van Fleet, Jo
      Van Loon, Hendrik Wilhelm
      Venuta, Benay
      Verdon, Gwen (see also: Box 6)
      Villard
      Von Furstenberg, Betsy
      Voskovec, George
    - Caricatures, Wager - Whorf, undated (Box 3)
      Wager, Michael
      Wakefield, Anne
      Walker, Nancy
      Walkowitz
      Wallach, Eli
      Walston, Ray
      Waram, Percy
      Waters, Ethel
      Watson, Lucille (see also: Lucas, Paul and Lucille Watson)
      Wayne, David
      Weaver, Fritz
      Webb, Clifton
      Welles, Orson
      Wescott, Mary
      Westman, Nydia
      Whalen, Grover
      Wheeler, Bert (see: Box 6)
      Wheeler, Wayne B.
      Whiting, Jack (see also: Box 6)
      Whitman, Ex-Governor
      Whorf, Richard
    - Caricatures, de Wild - Zimbalist, circa 1906-1961, undated (Box 3)
      de Wild, Brandon
      Willard, E. S.
      Williams, Herb
      Williams, John
      Wilson, Dooley
      Winters, Shelley
      Winwood, Estelle
      Wise, Thomas
      Wiseman, Joseph
      Withers, Googie (see also: Box 6)
      Wood, Peggy
      Worth, Irene
      Wortman, Denys
      Wortman, Hilda
      Wright, Frank Lloyd
      Wright, Teresa
      Wyatt, Jane
      Wynn, Ed (see also: Box 6)
      Yamada, Otsuzo
      Young, Gig
      Yurka, Blanche
      Zack, Max
      Zakkai, Jamie
      Zimbalist, Efrem
    - Caricatures, Unidentified Cast of Unknown Play, undated, (see: OV 9) (Box 3)
    - Caricatures, Unidentifed Men, undated (Box 3)
    - Caricatures, Unidentified Women, undated, (see also: Box 6) (Box 3)
    - Caricatures - Preliminary Drawings and Sketches ("The Corn is Green" and unidentified play), circa 1940, undated (Box 3)
    - Cartoons, undated, (4 folders) (Box 3)
    - Cartoons, 1955, undated, (see: Box 6) (Box 3)
    - Cover Designs (Stage Folk: A Book of Caricature by Frueh, The Penguin, and "Arts Ball"), circa 1922, undated (Box 3)
    - Drawings, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3)
    - Exhibition Announcement Design, Society of Independent Artists 6th Annual Exhibition, 1922 (Box 3)
    - Greeting Cards and Card Designs (Box 3)
      - Birthday, undated (Box 3)
      - Christmas, 1910, 1915, undated, (see also: Box 6) (Box 3)
      - Christmas; Get Well, 1928, 1941, undated, (see: Box 6) (Box 3)
      - Easter, undated (Box 3)
      - Get Well, undated, (see also: Box 6) (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947, 1955, undated (Box 3)
      - Valentines, undated (Box 3)
    - Lamp Base Sketches, undated (Box 3)
    - Lamp Shade Design, undated (Box 3)
    - Magic Square Designs and Patterns, undated (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous Art Work, undated, (see: Box 6) (Box 3)
    - Paper Sculpture Designs and Patterns, undated, (see: Box 6) (Box 3)
    - Pop-Ups and Cut-Outs, circa 1916, undated (Box 3)
    - Prints, undated, (see also: OV 8) (Box 3)
    - Sheet Material Sculptures and Toy Animals, undated, (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - Wallpaper Design ("Red Baron"), undated (Box 3)
    - Watercolors, 1913, undated, (see also: Box 6) (Box 3)
    - Oversized Caricatures, Anderson - Logan, undated (Box 6 (sol))
      Anderson, Judith
      Andrews, Julie
      Arden, Eve
      Barrymore, Ethel
      Bigley, Isabel
      Brando, Marlon
      Brown, Vanessa
      Cornell, Katharine
      Emerson, Faye
      Hartman, Paul
      Homolka, Oscar
      Kennedy, Arthur
      Lawrence, Gertrude
      Lindsay, Howard
      Logan, Ella
    - Oversized Caricatures, Massey - Wynn; Unidentified, undated (Box 6 (sol))
      Massey, Raymond
      Meacham, Anne
      Merivale, Phillip
      Mitchell, Thomas
      Palence, Walter Jack
      Portman, Eric
      Prokofiev, Sergei
      Rule, Janice
      Segal, Vivienne
      "Show Boat"
      Smith, Muriel
      Stickney, Dorothy
      Taylor, Laurette and Florence Reed
      Ure, Mary
      Verdon, Gwen
      Wheeler, Bert
      Whiting, Jack
      Withers, Googie
      Wynn, Ed
      Unidentified Women
    - Cartoons, 1955, undated (Box 6 (sol))
    - Cover Designs (Stage Folk: A Book of Caricature by Frueh, The Penguin, and "Arts Ball"), circa 1922, undated (Box 6 (sol))
    - Greeting Cards and Card Designs, Christmas and Get Well, 1928, 1941, undated (Box 6 (sol))
    - Miscellaneous Art Work, undated (Box 6 (sol))
    - Paper Sculpture Designs and Patterns, undated (Box 6 (sol))
    - Water Colors, undated (Box 6 (sol))
    - Oversized Caricatures (Unidentified Cast of Unknown Play), undated (Box OV 9)
  - By Others, undated, Subseries 4.2:
    - Caricature of Alfred Frueh (by Albert Bloch), undated (Box 6 (sol))
- Printed Material, 1904-1986, undated, Series 5:; (Boxes 4-5, 6, OV 10-12; 0.9 linear ft.)
  - Article by Frueh ("Stalking the Drummer," Outdoor Life), 1937 (Box 4 (hol))
  - Articles About/Mentioning Frueh or Containing Reproductions of his Work, 1905-1924, undated, (see: Box 6 and OV 10) (Box 4 (hol))
  - Articles About/Mentioning Frueh or Containing Reproductions of his Work, 1915-1991, undated, (3 folders) (Box 4 (hol))
  - Articles about The New Yorker, circa 1934, 1955, undated, (see: Box 6) (Box 4 (hol))
  - Book Cover Designed by Frueh (Stage Folk: A Book of Caricatures by Frueh), 1922, (see: Box 6) (Box 4 (hol))
  - Book Jackets Designed by Frueh (Log of the Ark and Fun Shop), 1915, circa 1927 (Box 4 (hol))
  - Caricatures by Frueh (Box 4 (hol))
    - Art Instruction, Art Review, Boston Evening Transcript, Cartoons Magazine, 1919-1938, undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - Life, 1921-circa 1922, undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - New Yorker ("Profiles"), 1925-1961, undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - New Yorker ("The Theatre"), 1927-1961, undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - New York Times, Overset, Pagan, Partisan Daily, Playboy, Quill, and St. Louis Dramatic News, 1908-1925, undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - St. Louis Post-Dispatch (A-Z), circa 1905-1908, 1912 (Box 4 (hol))
    - Sharon Playhouse, "Caricatures of the Theatre," circa 1950 (Box 4 (hol))
    - Washington Post (Teapot Dome/Falls-Sinclair Oil Trial), 1926-1927 (Box 4 (hol))
    - World; New York World-Telegram, 1915-1932, undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - World Magazine, 1918, (see: Box 6) (Box 4 (hol))
    - Unidentified Publications (A-Z by sitter), undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - Reference Material for Caricatures (A-Z by sitter), 1932-1950, undated (Box 4 (hol))
  - Cartoons by Frueh (Box 4 (hol))
    - Life, 1924-1926, undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - New Yorker, 1925-1939, undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - St. Louis Post-Dispatch and Bell Syndicate, 1911, undated, (see: OV 11) (Box 4 (hol))
    - World; New York World-Telegram and Sun, 1910-1958, undated (Box 4 (hol))
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 1929, undated (Box 4 (hol))
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Announcement - Frueh Solo and Group Shows, circa 1912-1986 (Box 4 (hol))
  - Exhibition Catalogs - Other Artists, 1912-1963, (4 folders) (Box 5 (hol))
  - Exhibition Reviews, 1912-1922, undated, (see: OV 12) (Box 5 (hol))
  - Exhibition Reviews, circa 1912-1923, 1950s, undated (Box 5 (hol))
  - Illustrations by Frueh (Box 5 (hol))
    - The New Yorker, 1926-1929, undated (Box 5 (hol))
    - The St. Louis Post-Dispatch, 1904 (Box 5 (hol))
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 1917-1939, undated (Box 5 (hol))
  - Invitations and Announcements Designed by Frueh, 1918-1922, undated (Box 5 (hol))
  - Magazine Covers by Frueh (The World Magazine), 1918-1919, (see: Box 6) (Box 5 (hol))
  - Magazine Covers by Frueh (The Blindman, The New Yorker, Life), 1917-1926 (Box 5 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous Items - Art Related, 1923-1957, undated (Box 5 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous Items - Mentioning Frueh, 1973, undated (Box 5 (hol))
  - Program Designed by Frueh (Life with Father, Sharon Hospital, Sharon, Conn.), undated (Box 5 (hol))
  - Articles About or Mentioning Frueh, 1905-1925, undated (Box 6 (sol))
  - Articles About The New Yorker, circa 1934, 1955, undated (Box 6 (sol))
  - Book Cover by Frueh (Stage Folk: A Book of Caricatures by Frueh), 1922 (Box 6 (sol))
  - Caricatures by Frueh (The World Magazine), 1918 (Box 6 (sol))
  - Magazine Covers by Frueh (The World Magazine), 1918-1919 (Box 6 (sol))
- Photographs, circa 1919-circa 1960s, undated, Series 6:; (Box 5; 0.1 linear ft.)
  - Art Work by Frueh (Box 5)
    - Caricatures (A-Z), 1939, undated (Box 5)
    - Lamp Bases, undated (Box 5)
    - Paper Sculptures (patented 1919), undated (Box 5)
    - Toy Animals, undated (Box 5)
  - Frueh, Alfred, circa 1940s, undated (Box 5)
  - Frueh, Barbara (daughter), circa 1919 (Box 5)